  {
    "questions":
    [
        {
           
            "question":"What does the NFL stand for?",
          "correct": "National Football League",
            "answers": [
                {"choice":  "National Football League" },
              {"choice":   "Notorious Fancy Legends"},
               { "choice":  "National Futbol League"},
               { "choice":  "National Freeloaders League"}
            ]
        },
        {
             
        "question":"How many teams are in the NFL?", 
            "correct": "32",
            "answers": [
                 {"choice":  "34" },
              {"choice":   "48"},
               { "choice":  "32"},
               { "choice":  "56"}
            ]
         
        },
        {
           
        "question":"American Football is different than both ____ other types of football", 
             "correct": "Soccer and College Football",
            "answers": [
                {"choice":  "College Football and hacky sack" },
              {"choice":   "Soccer and College Football"},
               { "choice":  "Hockey and Soccer"},
               { "choice":  "College Football and Volleyball"}
            ]
           
         
        },
        {
           
        "question":"What is the name of this app?", 
            "correct": "Talk Turf",
             "answers": [
                   {"choice":  "Turf Talking" },
              {"choice":   "Sideline Speaking"},
               { "choice":  "Court Chat"},
               { "choice":  "Talk Turf"}
            ]
         
        },
        {
            
        "question":"What days of the week can you watch the game?", 
              "correct": "Sunday, Monday, Thursday",
             "answers": [
                  {"choice":  "Sunday, Monday, Thursday" },
              {"choice":   "Monday, Wednesday, Friday"},
               { "choice":  "Tuesday, Thursday, Saturday"},
               { "choice":  "Sunday only"}
            ]
          
         
        },
        {
             
        "question":"How many plays must you complete to score a touchdown with this app?", 
            "correct": "10",
            "answers": [
                  {"choice":  "12" },
              {"choice":   "10"},
               { "choice":  "5"},
               { "choice":  "1"}
            ]
            
         
        },
        {
            
        "question":"Where can you find the list of teams in their respective conferences and divisions?", 
            "correct": "Pick your team",
             "answers": [
                  {"choice":  "Playbook" },
              {"choice":   "Glossary"},
               { "choice":  "Player Stats"},
               { "choice":  "Pick your team"}
            ]
            
         
        },
        {
            
        "question":"Each conference is divided into 4 divisions. What are they?",
            "correct": "North, South, East, and West",
            "answers": [
                 {"choice":  "North, South, East, and West" },
              {"choice":   "Top, Bottom, Left, Right"},
               { "choice":  "Ladder 1, Ladder 2, Ladder 3, Ladder 4"},
               { "choice":  "Northeast, Southeast, Northwest, Southwest"}
            ]
            
         
        },
        {
            
        "question":"What are the two NFL conference names?",
             "correct": "American and National",
            "answers": [
                  {"choice":  "Art and Noodles " },
              {"choice":   "American and National"},
               { "choice":  "Aardvark and Neptune"},
               { "choice":  "American and Norwegian"}
           
            ]
           
         
        },
        {
             
        "question":"This app is teaching me about",
            "correct": "Football",
             "answers": [
                  {"choice":  "Rugby" },
              {"choice":   "Tennis"},
               { "choice":  "Football"},
               { "choice":  "Hockey "}
            ]

        }
        
    ]
}
        

